Hello there.
In this video, I will discuss about benefits and limitation of chat.
Now discuss about.
Benefit of chat, right?
Jeopardy is developed by openai.
We scan generate like human tests based on the input to recipes.
Some of the benefits of using Djibouti include natural language understanding.
Djibouti is strained on a large data set of human languages.
Making it capable of understanding natural language inputs and providing like human responses.
Automation.
Chad Djibouti allows marketers to automate repetitive tasks such as responding to frequently ask questions
or providing personalized recommendations to customers.
Versatility.
Chelsea Beauty can be used in a variety of application, including language, translation, text generation
and question answering.
Large data capacity.
Djibouti is trained on a large amount of data which allows it to have a vast knowledge and can answer
a variety of questions.
Cost effective.
Using DVT can be a cost effective solution for businesses.
Chad Djibouti can help marketers to save on labor cost and other expenses associated with managing customer
interactions.
This can help to improve the bottom line, making campaigns more profitable and sustainable.
According to Djibouti, can be integrated with different applications, platforms and services with
minimal.
Or no coding experience.
It can be used to build conversational AI, chat bot and other MPL applications.
High speed chat deputy can work quickly generating large amount of text in a short amount of time.
This can save time and increase efficiency or task such as data entry, content creation and customer
service.
Text generation chat activity can be used to generate a wide range of text, including article, blogpost,
product description and much more.
This can save time and effort for tasks such as content creation, copywriting and data entry, and
also last one flexibility.
Chat can be integrated into a range of marketing channels, including website, mobile apps and social
media platforms.
This allows marketers to connect with customers in the place where they are most likely to engage this,
providing a seamless and consistent experience across channels.
Chat activity is still in its early stages and is being updated and improved.
As a result, the accuracy, flexibility and other feature are expected to improve over time.
Now discuss about limitation of activity.
Look here please.
May occasionally generate incorrect information, may occasionally produce harmful instruction or based
content and also.
Limited knowledge of what and even after.
2021 Djibouti are not able to provide personal or emotional support or engages in depth conversations
about complex topics.
They are simply programmed to generate text based on pattern in the data they have been trained on.
Right.
Djibouti can generate incorrect response, confidently making it all the more difficult to trust.
For this reason, it is best used shadowed by a human.
So the most important risk, however, is that customer can mislead or even manipulate Djibouti to get
what they want, as I think it's the most important risk at the moment.
So I hope as soon as there was takeover in this hope, do you understand?
Benefit and limitation of chat GPT.
Thanks for watching this video.