Hello there.
In this lesson, I will teach you how to create chat account.
There are two processes.
Create an account.
Number one process.
You can visit that dot openai dot com or.
You can visit often a dot com.
So now here I live chat dot open a dot com and press enter.
So now this is just deputy account open interface right now Click sign up button.
And press here.
Email address.
And press.
Continue item and paste here your password.
And press continue button.
So at a few minutes look this verify your email.
We send an email to your email address.
This email.
Right.
So you need to check this email.
This is email come from openai dot com.
For verification, Right?
So now click this email and verify email address.
So here I open different browser.
Then I need to click.
Copy this link and open new tab and.
Best hair and dental.
So here is your first name and last name, right?
And press continuato and put her phone number right.
After putting your phone number, then you need to click.
Send code button here.
So now click it and check your phone number here.
Send the verification messages right now.
Here, I put my verification code.
And after verification code put, then it will be automatically redirect a chat.
Now next.
Next.
Done.
So friends, this is our chat gpg interface.
So here put any questions.
Ask chat.
Right.
Hopefully.
Do you understand how to create chat account on openai dot com.
Thanks for watching this video.