Welcome back.
In this video I will show you.
How to tour chat interface.
This is a chat interface.
Here are chat option and here dark and light mode.
If I click dark mode, then this screen automatically dark mode.
So click dark mode now.
Right.
And.
This option open, I discard and this update and if you so if I click update and if Q options, then
it will be shown new interface.
And here's some content and look right site.
Here.
Sure.
Messenger icon.
Right now, click here.
And maybe it will be contact, support or something like this nitwit for a second.
Now this is on tap option.
You can send a message here or a need help source button and now go back to the main interface.
And here I'll see new chat.
And that means when you hear ask any questions, then this title automatically.
Right here and said, Sepp, this.
Now here, ask some questions like.
Right there.
To reveal.
About.
iPhone 13 pro max and end enter.
So friends look this you are automatically generate content.
So I put a question here.
Then it will be automatic writer review.
So the iPhone 13 pro max is an impressive device with a sporting 6.8 inch full HD display, powerful
A15 bionic chip and 5G capabilities.
The camera system is top notch with a triple lens setup that includes a 12 MP ultra wide, wide and
telephoto lens.
So overall, the iPhone 13 pro max is a solid choice for anyone looking for a high end feature packed
smartphone.
So hopefully you understand how to use chat interface for your work purpose.
Thanks for watching this video.